瞧你这事儿砸的
You really dropped the ball, man.
闭嘴 你这小肚鸡肠的逼崽子
Shut up, Morty, you vindictive little turd!
你闭嘴 你个大母王八
You shut up, you big female asshole!
别推我
Hey, don't shove me!
- 我没有 - 什么你没有
- I didn't! - You didn't what?
- 你什么毛病 - 你又是什么毛病
- What's your problem? - What's yours?
- 闭嘴 - 你才闭嘴
- Shut up! - You shut up!
嗷 噢
-wh-whoa, whoa!
搞什么鬼鬼鬼鬼鬼
What the hell, hell, hell, hell, hell?
你们搞什么
Oh, god. Oh, no. What did you guys just do?
什么意思
what do you mean?
你说谁
What did who do?
等等 我在说什么
Wait, what am I saying?
刚才是不是有谁有什么不确定的事儿
Were either of you guys uncertain about anything just now?
天 我感觉好难受
Oh, man, I don't feel good.
我还是我吗
Am I me?
我在说话吗
Am I talking right now?
应该是吧
I think so.
谁在说话
Wait, who said that?
你们俩听好 先别动
All right, both of you just don't move.
别说话 也别瞎想 我去检查检查
Don't speak, don't think. I have to check something.